why are we having a conversation
all right before i get started just let
y'all know i'm i'm not darius rucker i'm
not
do not ask i'm not him all right
it's my first time in utah
[Applause]
yeah
i went to uh y'all target today
and i was playing this game when i was
in there called um
find the black dude
security was playing the same game
and uh
they won so
[Music]
it was crazy
i was almost late getting here man i was
nervous i thought i was going to be late
uh driving through utah and uh i had to
stop at one of your gas stations to get
gas and it took me 30 minutes to get gas
and uh i wasn't used to it i didn't know
if it was a utah thing but uh got to the
gas pump put my card in and they said
debit of credit and i said debit they
said what should code or put my code in
it's like what's your zip code i was
like i don't even live here what you
need to know my zip code for
now he's like you want a hot dog
i was like no i want to get some gas
he's like you want a car wash i'm like
no
they said we got fountain drinks inside
why are we having a conversation
you shop at smith's i don't live here
i hit the wrong button to cancel my
whole transaction huh
looking for the manager they didn't even
have a car wash i was like wait a minute
didn't you just ask me if i wanted a car
wash i started oh we don't go over again
it's like you want a car wash i said you
know what yes i want a car wash now what
and three mexicans walked out i said
this is
the mexican dude was cool though he was
just telling me that the car washes
behind the gas station but i like how
y'all laugh cause i thought they came
out to watch my car
that was the test y'all felt that
miserably y'all
i'm not judging this early all right
recently single again i don't like being
single i don't like the whole dating
thing the reason why i don't like dating
is because i always end up dating a
ghetto chick but i never know she ghetto
in the beginning i don't find out till
way later when she get comfortable with
the date and she'll just hit me with a
ghetto smack out of nowhere
some of y'all got quiet like y'all know
what that is
that's when the girl is so involved in
her conversation she has to stop talking
to gather her spit together and then
continue on with the conversation and
it'll catch you off guard if you never
heard her before but it sounds something
like this so it was me nikki and shay
right
i said did you just hit me with a ghetto
smack she was like no i thought you said
we were going to a
restaurant i said oh we are she said
where are we going i said mcdonald's now
she said oh good because i was hungry
let me get a double cheeseburger oh
a large fry
i said get out my car
it was crazy i had to start dating black
girls again i was like i can't keep
putting up with this every time
some of y'all look confused on that one
don't worry about it you'll figure it
out later
[Music]
i am the proud parent of twin daughters
i have twin girls um beautiful ladies
thank you thank you um
amazing thing about my twins is that
they're fraternal twins now one of my
daughters looks just like me and one of
my daughters looks just like my ex-wife
now the twin that look like me acts just
like me the one that looked like his
wife acts exactly like my ex-wife and my
twins argue with each other all the time
and i said wow i hadn't seen all this
before
give her like two and a half more years
somebody gotta file for divorce like
this is not gonna work out we
set you all up for failure we're sorry
you know
the one that act like me like daddy she
always got to be right she always
arguing when she won't never be quiet i
was like look sometimes you just gotta
grab your car keys and just walk the
hell out like you don't
you don't have to put up with that stop
crying stand up for yourself be a man
i'm glad my daughters are older though
i'm glad they're older because i don't
have to watch nick jr anymore in my
house
like for the first five years of their
life i was the goofiest dad of all time
nobody can debate me on this okay like
i'll be in the house all of a sudden the
phone rings
the phone
the phone is ringing
will be right there
the phone
the phone is ringing
there's an animal in trouble somewhere
sir don't look at me like i just made
that song up all right i'm not the only
one here that knows that song all right
you don't believe me watch this what's
going to work
get ain't the new jay-z man that's
that's parents in 101 right there
they used to watch this show called yo
gabba gabba
they had this real flamboyant black dude
on there with this tight orange suit on
be yelling at the tv like let's go over
what we did today can you help me and
all the kids be like yeah
can we dance and the kids go yeah
they'll go well let's do it or break it
down
my daughter's be like daddy break it
go to bed
but their favorite show was this show
called the backyardigans all right and
this little
uh show about these animals at the
backyard to make believe but the animals
on the show was black but they didn't
tell you the animals was black but once
you saw the show you knew they was black
because the moose name was tyrone i was
like all right
it might be a token i'm not going to
judge
then they had a hippopotamus named tasha
i was like okay that's a pattern
this one i knew they was all black they
had this pink thing on there i don't
even know what she was her name was
uniqua
i was like okay so y'all went the whole
way all right
you always know the show was about to go
off at the end because they would ask
for a snack when they asked for a snack
that means a show by the golf my kids
ask for snacks all the time i'm like why
y'all keep asking snacks it's cause
they're watching this goofy show and i
don't know about y'all y'all might have
been rich when y'all grew up but i
didn't grow up in a house with a whole
bunch of snacks okay my sister coming
out video mommy just bought some cookies
like first of all it ain't even a
holiday don't mess with me like that you
know
kids get snacks all the time now it's
like a requirement you know what i mean
my kids outside playing one day this
little girl at the end of my driveway i
don't even know this little girl i get
to the end of the driveway she's like
how are you doing i was like fine nice
to meet you she's like y'all got any
snacks in your house
i was like bye felicia
get your biggest self out of my driveway
she's like i just want to know if y'all
got any snacks
say we ain't got jack snaggy robinson
get your behind on my driveway
when my kids were six years old man i
had the opportunity of a lifetime got a
chance to take it to disney world they
know they was going the best day of
their life got to disney world man the
best day that we were down there they
got a chance to uh put their princess
dresses on and meet all the disney
princesses in one day lost their minds
they saw snow white they was like
they saw cinderella there's like oh my
gosh she's real
they saw ariel they was like she's
walking
and then jasmine came out and i was like
wow
i was like she looked bad at zach in
real life
i was like oh my god i can't get a
picture with you she was like sure i was
like oh my god
there's like daddy want to picture with
jasmine i was like shut up
i said you guys excuse me my nieces be
trippin they
wow
as a father though you always want to
make sure you're protecting your
daughters that's our main goal as a
father protect your children it was a
situation that happened when they were
smaller and i wasn't able to protect
them the way i was supposed to and it
bothered me you know we driving in the
car one day they in the back singing
having a good time all of a sudden they
start screaming at the top of their
lungs
daddy i turn around i said what's the
problem it's like daddy it's a bug in
the car and i turn this little tiny bug
flying in the back seat of the car and i
said don't worry about it mama daddy can
fix it i put the window down in the
backyard a little bug flew out
then this big bug flew in
they lost their minds
they were screaming they was kicking the
back of my ceiling so hurry stop
screaming and shut up sit down to be
quiet on the beach
turn around i put the windows up in the
back i said now look neither y'all gonna
kill this bug
or the bug gonna kill y'all
y'all they straight murdered that bug
you hear me
like how y'all get out the seat belt
that fast
put the knife down
one of my daughters is extremely smart
i'm not saying my other daughter is dumb
i'm saying one is extremely smart okay
now figure this out now i'll give you a
good example like my daughter one of my
daughters is right reading level right
math level everything is right where
it's supposed to be but my other
daughter is on some astronaut stuff and
i just figured it out when they're about
three years old we're in a restaurant
both my daughter said at the same time
daddy we have to go to the bathroom and
i was like this is horrible because
don't know dad when i had to take his
daughters into no men's bathroom so i'm
like look don't nobody look at nothing
don't nobody touch nothing matter of
fact don't even touch each other because
i don't know how this works okay
so we get in the bathroom and they use
the bathroom we walk out to the sink
they're washing their hands
and all of a sudden my daughter who's
three years old was trying to read the
sign on the wall and i was like wow
she's trying to read the sign of the
sink she's only three years old i'm
impressed a couple minutes later my
daughter was like daddy why do employees
have to wash their hands before
returning to work i was like what
i said you just read that she said yes
sir and i started tripping because i'm
like maybe i could read at three
i just only remember having to read in
kindergarten you understand what i'm
saying but nobody remembers being three
you know what i mean but i got another
three-year-old right beside her another
crash dummy right there i'm like hey
can you read that sign she said yes sir
i said what's it say she said brown
i said not the color what's the word say
she said white
i said you can't read that she's like
i'm three i said that's what i thought
don't touch her she a mutant that's
exactly what i thought
ever since that moment man my daughter
has found a way to make me feel dumb
every single year without even trying
right last year my daughters wanted
wristwatches for christmas right so i
was like i got an idea i'll pick them up
one weekend we'll go to the mall go
through the store look at some watches
then i know what to get what not to get
for christmas right we get to the third
store my daughter goes oh i said what's
the problem she's like where are the
analog watches
i said who makes that
she an analog i said what is that timex
rolex hublot who makes that she said
analog daddy i was like what are you
talking about she said these are digital
i was like and she's like the other
watch longhand shorthand
i said who told you that she's like
that's what we learned in school i said
that's wrong
she said what's it called i said it's
called a regular watch
she's like it's not i said it is i
called my ex-wife on the phone i said
hey the watch was just the numbers on it
what's that called she said digital i
said the one with the long handed short
hand
i said what's that called she's like a
regular watch i said that's what i
thought
i just want to make sure two dumb
parents can make a smart kid is what i
was trying to figure out
now with twins everything is a
competition you know they com
everything's competitive and my other
daughter is tired of hearing how smart
her sister is she want to get some
praise so one day my daughter comes and
goes daddy guess what the teacher said i
said what the teacher said she said the
teacher said i have the neatest
handwriting in the whole grade i said
the whole grade she said the whole grade
i said write something for me she wrote
something i made a big deal about it i
said wow that's beautiful i never seen
somebody your age write that meat before
that's absolutely amazing her sister
goes
i said what's the problem she's like her
her tittles aren't even in the right
position i said her what
she said her tittles i was like what's
that she said that's the dot over top of
the lowercase i i said you just making
stuff up now
she's like look it up i go on my phone
i'm looking it up but as i'm looking it
up i'm telling her hey here's a
situation you could have happily been
happy for your sister and just gave her
some praise instead of trying to be a
jerk and trying to make her feel bad
about herself i was like and i'm looking
this information up and i'm reading the
definition and you owe her an apology
cause that's not what it means she said
you spelled it incorrectly
i said you better get out my face
before i put a tittle over your eyes you
know
been doing comedy for a while man i do a
lot of traveling there's a lot of
stories on the road which is always fun
i'll share a couple of them with you i
was doing a show one time in myrtle
beach south carolina doing this show i
was out one afternoon having lunch and i
was leaving this restaurant the same
time this older couple was leaving and
this older couple had been together at
least 40 years you could just tell by
their mannerisms how they treated one
another but they were still holding
hands and i'm like that is beautiful
they're walking out the restaurant but
it was pouring down raining and the wife
turned her husband and said baby it's
really coming down out there why don't
you go get the car and pull it around so
i can get in and i was like that's so
sweet
he turned around looked at his wife and
was like what you just in the ocean an
hour ago
go outside get in the car
and she walked out in the ring and i i
said what was that i was mad cause i was
like i've seen notebook way too many
times that's not supposed to happen
after 40 years you know
hurt my heart you know
i was doing a show one time in virginia
it was a real small crowd maybe 10 or 15
people and i met this couple up front i
said hey y'all cute where'd y'all meet
they said work i said where do you work
they said high school so i asked the
lady what exactly do you do at the high
school she said i'm an interpreter i
translate i said would he translate
spanish she said no sign language i said
oh how many deaf kids they got at the
school she said one
i said so if that kid don't come to
school you get to go home she's like
yeah i said wow
that's a great job you know i signed
that kid every other thursday like look
now you know we ain't got no school
tomorrow right
who's going to verify that you
understand what i'm saying
like they didn't come to school again
but like dude three day weekend don't
get mad at me i don't know where that
kid is you know
but i've always wanted to tell jokes and
have somebody do sign language on stage
but we never had anybody deaf in the
audience but that night i had an
interpreter so i pulled her up on stage
just to test it out so i started telling
my jokes she was signing every single
word to precision crowd is laughing but
this how dumb the crowd was they weren't
laughing when they heard my joke they
would wait till she got done
and then they would laugh
and i'm like what the heck are y'all
doing
y'all not deaf and y'all don't know sign
language what you waiting on her for you
know
and i'm telling these jokes that she all
animated behind me and they laughing at
her and i'm like that's not how it's
supposed to work at all
because if it was a deaf person in the
audience i would tell the joke y'all
would laugh and then i would hear
after
some of y'all tightened up on that one
listen
they are never going to hear that joke
all right so
relax
stop judging
and enjoy yourself okay
[Music]
i find out a lot of good stuff on the
road too man
uh educational stuff i was doing a show
one time in alabama and i met this lady
at the end of the show and she said i
just moved down here from the northeast
i said why'd you move down to alabama
she said i'm helping my brother with
some animals and i was like what does he
have a farm she said nah he just got
some farm animals
i said what's he have she's like oh he
got some chickens he got some goats got
a couple sheep got some horses i was
like that's a farm
she's like he got a donkey i was like
why does he have a donkey she's like oh
that's a guard animal it protects the
other animals that's like no it doesn't
yeah dude look it up i looked it up i
never knew this in my entire life
that donkeys are very territorial
animals and if you raise donkeys around
other animals they become protective of
them so if that's a coyote or a fox or
anything a round of danger the coyote
will chase it'll bite it'll kick it'll
break real loud brain is he on i thought
it was called he hung but it ain't
i didn't know nothing about donkeys okay
like the only thing i knew about donkeys
i swear to god then only thing i knew
about donkeys was that they talk like
eddie murphy
they hang with shrek
and they marry dragons like that's the
only
thing i knew about donkeys and i'm
reading all the pros they have in the
donkey and i'm saying to myself i should
buy a donkey like they might be the next
pit bull you don't know right
so they had all the pros listed for
having a donkey and next to the pros
they had the cons the cons for having a
donkey are they might not do none of the
things i just said they were supposed to
do
so you can go to the donkey dealership
and buy you a brand new donkey right
raise this donkey for two years right
you wake up one morning everything that
hit the fan right
the chickens are slaughtered the goat is
gone the horse is missing
the donkey eating you like what happened
in the donkey like man it went down last
night
it went down you didn't do your donkey
stuff for nothing
nah
you know what you being right now
you're lucky i can't say it
yeah they call me that too
it's amazing man
donkeys right
it's good stuff man i uh
as a parent man i uh and everybody in
here is parents clap your hands parents
anywhere
i give you guys respect because you all
try you try your best to do the best job
you can and none of us are perfect we
all make mistakes you just want to make
sure you don't make the huge mistake
that's going to screw your kids up for
the rest of their life
i did something a few weeks ago y'all
it's questionable okay but i'm telling
y'all not for y'all to judge me just so
i can get it off my chest okay we all
friends now all right
me and my daughters were walking into a
grocery store and it was an asian family
walking out as we were walking in and
the asian family all had germ masks on
and my daughters had never seen that
before and my daughter was like daddy
why are they wearing those masks and i
could have been a good parent at that
point
all i had to do was explain to them that
hey in the asian culture is so populated
they wear those masks as a courtesy so
they don't pass their germs on back and
forth on another when they have a cold
or they sick but i didn't say that
i said they on their way to ninja
practice
i went for the funny right i'm a
comedian right but then my conscience
said hey you're a jerk you just pass
prejudices only your kids and they gonna
think that for the rest of their life
because you trying to be funny
then my conscience went a step further
and said now what if the little asian
girl asked her dad at the very same time
daddy why are they all wearing hoodies
going into the store
and the dad said easy they bout to rob
it
now the message is
don't pass prejudices on to your kids
cause it's just not fair to them okay
all right thank you
but don't act like the next time y'all
don't see a germ mash i'm not gonna be
like
ninja practice
that was good man i uh
tattoos clap your hands tattoos in the
house tattoos all right maybe one person
i see
that's how y'all get down to utah
like we got the one person i gotta
tattoo over here that's what it is
don't worry i don't have one i don't
have one either so i'm kind of with
y'all but i always wanted to get one but
i always was afraid i was gonna get one
that's gonna be messed up and then i
gotta live with it for the rest of my
life got a friend of mine she was all
excited one day i said what you all
happy about she said i'm about to go to
this tattoo party and i said what is a
tattoo party she said i got a friend of
mine that want to be a tattoo artist
throw these parties on the weekends and
give everybody a free tattoo so we can
practice
i said you mean like with a sharpie
she said no with a real tattoo gun i
said what they look like she said they
getting better
i said are you crazy she's like no it's
free i said that's not what i asked you
i asked you if you was crazy she's like
it's free i was like whatever i said
what you gonna get she said i'ma let him
decide i said
you're crazy that's easy right a couple
days later she come to the house smiling
i said what'd you get she said my zodiac
sign i said let me see she took her
shirt sleeve down on her arm her tattoo
said leo
had a leo symbol had a lion underneath
it but the lion had a massive massive
underbite
her lion had an uncorrectable underbite
okay
like every time she moved her arm and
like the lion was singing and you whoo
i said even if the top part of your arm
got fat right here his jaw is still
gonna be messed up
she said i think you look cute i said i
think you need to cut your arm off i'm
just
a couple days later a couple days later
my boy came over the house had the same
arm bandaged up and i said what happened
in your arm he said i went to this free
tattoo party
i said what'd you get he said my zodiac
sign i said you lying i said would you
i said what'd you get he's my zodiac
sign i said man please let me see this
tattoo
i said you're not a leo are you he's
like nah i said let me see took his
shirt off took the bandage off on his
tattoo it said aquarius
had the aquarius symbol
had the same lion
with a swim cap on i sit down
it's not aquarius
i know we going through like a lot of
political things and i feel like
sometimes i need to be a politician
because i have a lot of great ideas and
i think my ideas will bring everybody
together because when i come up with my
ideas i include everybody every
demographic i just do things that make
sense to everybody i got two good ideas
if i come up with four more
i might be your next president i'm just
letting y'all know
i might start right here in utah yes
damn
my first idea is i think they need to
come out with an update on social media
that allows everyone to update their
friend's post
like for grammatical errors
like if you can't properly use there
there or there in a sentence
you should get off social media you know
what i mean like at least off my
timeline right
i had a friend of mine that died a few
weeks ago and somebody put on my post
hey
sorry for your lost
and i said yeah man he not missing he
gone
and some of y'all didn't laugh at that
if you don't fully understand that joke
let's just say you lost all right let's
my second idea is i think they needed to
come out with a law that requires
everyone to put their cell phone number
on a license plate
stop a traffic jam immediately you call
some on the phone
hello hey man you know anybody that owns
a great range rover or blue corvette no
exactly you don't know no people in that
accident keep it moving
got all this backed up cause you being
nosey get out of the way
on the highway it'd be ten times better
you're on the highway
hello hey man what's going on who this
don't worry about who it is
what i need you to get your dumb behind
out this left lane
and get over
hey man i'm going up they'll tell me how
fast she was going you ain't seen me
hyping like a mile back man get over hey
man you ain't got to get belligerent hey
man don't get mad at the messenger man
the dude behind me called me to call you
to tell you
thank you you saw man your god
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign